[
  {
    "question": "When was Alice born?",
    "answers": [
      "16th Jan 1993",
      "15th Jan 1995",
      "16th Jan 1994",
      "15th Jan 1994"
    ],
    "correct": 2
  },
  {
    "question": "Who did Alice kiss on her 18th birthday?",
    "answers": [
      "David Young",
      "David Weatherill (Peak moment)",
      "Tom Branigan",
      "Connor McManus"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "What mistake did Alice make in Bulgaria?",
    "answers": [
      "Not enough suncream!!!",
      "Making much noise after midnight (50lv fine)",
      "Throwing a sunbed in the pool (50lv fine)",
      "Running naked (50lv fine)"
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How did she manage to get a free drink at The George?",
    "answers": [
      "Flashing George",
      "Running naked (50lv fine)",
      "Stole it from behind the bar",
      "Kissing the bartender"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How many 'official team rules' has Alice broken?",
    "answers": [
      "0 - she's an angel",
      "1",
      "All of them, that slut",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "How many men has Alice got with after another team member has already got with them?",
    "answers": [
      "0 - she's an angel",
      "1",
      "All of them, that slut",
      "3"
    ],
    "correct": 3
  },
  {
    "question": "What has Alice tried to hide under Sophie's pillows?",
    "answers": [
      "Her puke",
      "A large vibrator",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which is the correct order for Alice's exes?",
    "answers": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "How long did Alice date Alex?",
    "answers": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of Alice's exes had the biggest penis?",
    "answers": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Who is Alice's most shameful conquest?",
    "answers": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
  {
    "question": "Where did Alice take Tom's virginity?",
    "answers": [
      "That tent in Ben's field",
      "Classy A41 Premiere Inn",
      "Tom's parents bed",
      "Tom's minty shit of a car"
    ],
    "correct": 1
  },
  {
    "question": "How many virginity's has Alice taken?",
    "answers": [
      "",
      "",
      "",
      ""
    ],
    "correct": 0
  },
]
